# ISMAEEL AKRAM

#### **FULL-STACK DEVELOPER**

(718) 314-5361 IsmaeelAkram.com

ismaeel@ismaeelakram.com Linkedin: IsmaeelAkram

### **Profile**

I am a full-stack developer living in New York City. I specialize in web development, app development, backend development, data/server management, databasing, and UI/UX design. My work is specifically created for the ease of the user and I simplify all tasks as much as I can.

#### **Education**

2020 - 2024

Brooklyn Technical High School

#### **Skills**

JavaScript	
Python	
C++	
C#	
Java	
CSS	
HTML	
ReactJS	
React Native	
SQL	
MongoDB	
Firebase	
AWS	
DigitalOcean	

## **Experience**

April 2020 - Present Lead Full-Stack Developer / Owner — **Plantify** 

Plantify is a mobile app that helps people keep their plants green. It is available on the iOS App Store and Google Play Store. Plantify uses React Native and Firebase.

June 2020 - Present Frontend Web Developer — **Foundry** 

Foundry is a social media platform for Brooklyn Tech students to share, grow, and discuss together. Foundry uses ReactJS and Firebase.

March 2020 - Present Lead Full-Stack Developer / Owner — **Count** 

Count is a mobile app that helps people count up their cash efficiently and easily. It is available for free on the Google Play Store. Count uses React Native.

December 2019 - Present Lead Developer — **Launchnow** 

Launchnow is an open source endeavor that allows automatic deployment without a CI/CD pipeline! It uses a simple command-line interface to interact with the server